Preliminary guide to the James Goode papers, Circa 1860-2018 MS0670.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence, 1953-2017; 1955-2017; Series 8; 18 Linear Feet
  - Incoming correspondence, 1953-2017; 1955-2017; Series 8 subseries 2; 16.75 Linear Feet
    - Correspondence, 2012; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2013; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2014; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2015; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2016-2017; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Paul Deaton, 2017; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Historical Society of Wash. D.C., 2006; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Car Show Cocktail Party Invite, 2017; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Seale, Wm, 2003-2013; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Family correspondence, 1944-2000; Subseries 3; 0.25 Linear Feet 1 letter size document box
    This series is comprised of approximately 200 photocopies of letters between various members of the family of James Goode dating from 1944-2002. Topics covered include: conditions James Goode faced growing up in Hickory, North Carolina(1939-1958), his early college years(1957-1958) and his three years in the U.S. Army (1958-1961).
    Series: Arranged by family member, original order created by the donor.
    - Miscellaneous family correspondence, circa 1950- circa 1970 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      Contains outgoing correspondence from James Goode to his parents and brother George.
    - Mrs. Thelma Wagg, 1952-1994 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      "Letters from Mrs. Thelma Wagg, Greensbow N.C., later Mrs. George Smothers."
    - Mrs. George B. Goode (Box 95, Folder 2)
      "Letters from mother, Mrs. George B. Goode "Dot" ."
    - Mrs. George B. Goode, part 2, 1956-1963 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. Thomas V. Goode II, 1959-1964 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      "Letters from Mrs. Thomas Vance Goode II, Statesville, N.C.. Wife of Dr. Thomas V. Goode II, daddy's older brother."
    - Mrs. Thomas Vance Goode, Sr., 1944 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Letters from Mrs. Thomas Vance Goode, Morganton, N.C., grandmother "mama Goode".
    - Thelma Goode, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      Letters from Miss Thelma Goode, Morganton, N.C., daddy's youngest sister.
    - Mrs. Gustav Kastner, 1956-1959 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      Letters from Gustav Kastner of Louisville, KY. Mother's sister (Dick).
    - Mrs. Arch Wilson, 1959-1992 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      Letters from Mrs. Arch Wilson, Mother's sister Louisburg, N.C., "Mike".
    - Mrs. John R. Simons, 1957-1984 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      Letters from Mrs. John Ross Simons, Greensbow, N.C. and Hopler, Fla. Mother's sister "Betty" and "Bib".
    - Mrs. Rush Duncan, 8/1957 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - James M. Goode, part I, 1957-1982 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      Letters from James M. Goode to family members, part I.
    - James M. Goode, part II, 1958-1961 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      Lettes from James M. Goode to family members, part II